<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://mstewartgallus.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://mstewartgallus.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-10-19T17:32:02-07:00</updated><id>https://mstewartgallus.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Molossus Spondee</title><subtitle>estoric poetry, occultism, weird trans category theory software stuff</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Emotion Exercise</title><link href="https://mstewartgallus.github.io/prose/2019/2022/10/19/emotion-exercise.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Emotion Exercise" /><published>2022-10-19T17:14:00-07:00</published><updated>2022-10-19T17:14:00-07:00</updated><id>https://mstewartgallus.github.io/prose/2019/2022/10/19/emotion-exercise</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mstewartgallus.github.io/prose/2019/2022/10/19/emotion-exercise.html">&lt;p&gt;I feel a great heaviness about my eyes and tension is jamming needles in my jaw.
&lt;br /&gt;My arms are all itchy red and swollen up and tension crushes the muscles of my back together.
&lt;br /&gt;The ground beneath my feet is very heavy and weighs down on me so much.
&lt;br /&gt;My gut grinds together and my burning parched throat chokes itself.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have a bit of a sinus headache and my face is itchy all over.
&lt;br /&gt;My legs itch, my arms itch, my body itches, my face itches.
&lt;br /&gt;I feel despondent, glum.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I feel very ugly inside and out.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I breathe shallowly with a racing heartbeat.
&lt;br /&gt;I don&apos;t know when the tiredness will ever leave my eyes.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tendons of my forearms are tense, my shoulders are tense, my whole body is tensed.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="prose" /><category term="2019" /><summary type="html">I feel a great heaviness about my eyes and tension is jamming needles in my jaw. My arms are all itchy red and swollen up and tension crushes the muscles of my back together. The ground beneath my feet is very heavy and weighs down on me so much. My gut grinds together and my burning parched throat chokes itself.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Night Ghost</title><link href="https://mstewartgallus.github.io/poetry/2019/the-night-ghost/2022/10/19/the-night-ghost.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Night Ghost" /><published>2022-10-19T12:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2022-10-19T12:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://mstewartgallus.github.io/poetry/2019/the-night-ghost/2022/10/19/the-night-ghost</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mstewartgallus.github.io/poetry/2019/the-night-ghost/2022/10/19/the-night-ghost.html">&lt;p&gt;The bungler in the grip of the demon held
&lt;br /&gt;To his crypt by strange means is compelled
&lt;br /&gt;And sleeping as a corpse in darkness rotting
&lt;br /&gt;He dreams forth the red eyed thing
&lt;br /&gt;So rises from the sleeper&apos;s breath
&lt;br /&gt;Comes the Night Ghost - who brings death!
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Night Ghost climbs, as a shadow leaping, overtop the manor wall
&lt;br /&gt;And through an open window goes, as a chilling fog
&lt;br /&gt;To the room of the sleeper he creeps
&lt;br /&gt;And as a swarm of bugs, overtop her stomach crawls
&lt;br /&gt;And on her chest, as a choking darkness sits
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&apos;Til she wakes with a gasp
&lt;br /&gt;The Night Ghost; by the window watching, giant as a shadow standing
&lt;br /&gt;She claps &lt;clap sound effect&gt; turning on the light
&lt;br /&gt;And The Night Ghost, as the darkness in the day, vanishes from all sight.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><category term="2019" /><category term="the-night-ghost" /><summary type="html">The bungler in the grip of the demon held To his crypt by strange means is compelled And sleeping as a corpse in darkness rotting He dreams forth the red eyed thing So rises from the sleeper&apos;s breath Comes the Night Ghost - who brings death!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Slow Rot</title><link href="https://mstewartgallus.github.io/poetry/the-slow-rot/2019/2022/10/18/the-slow-rot.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Slow Rot" /><published>2022-10-18T18:32:00-07:00</published><updated>2022-10-18T18:32:00-07:00</updated><id>https://mstewartgallus.github.io/poetry/the-slow-rot/2019/2022/10/18/the-slow-rot</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mstewartgallus.github.io/poetry/the-slow-rot/2019/2022/10/18/the-slow-rot.html">&lt;p&gt;The slow rot
&lt;br /&gt;lived or died, it&apos;s hard to tell
&lt;br /&gt;And fires lost away / down to hell
&lt;br /&gt;And as wind trow to take / hero&apos;s hearth
&lt;br /&gt;To slimy lair / past danger&apos;s berth
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shepherd, lay, in drunken stupor
&lt;br /&gt;As wind waste fire back away
&lt;br /&gt;So the nimble thief he plot to fire hold
&lt;br /&gt;To rob chilly&apos;s empty hall of filth and cold
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Through rot and ruin barely seeing
&lt;br /&gt;In darkness scarce light flickers fleeing
&lt;br /&gt;So journeyed Bound in circles round
&lt;br /&gt;The hunter searched, following found
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Winged death, stumbling, the cripple come!
&lt;br /&gt;The slow rot, silent, cold and numb
&lt;br /&gt;All gravid full of piss and shit
&lt;br /&gt;He bit, swallowed, spit
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But thief rallied, brandished knife and struck
&lt;br /&gt;Yet the wound was
&lt;br /&gt;Not hot and bleeding / but rotting, eating
&lt;br /&gt;The orc only coughed and shook
&lt;br /&gt;And yet more the cunning man he ate and took
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hands deep pocketed inside his guts
&lt;br /&gt;The thief struck with cuts and cuts
&lt;br /&gt;And heart in hand took torch to scour
&lt;br /&gt;So doctor kills doctor kills doctor&apos;s power!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><category term="the-slow-rot" /><category term="2019" /><summary type="html">The slow rot lived or died, it&apos;s hard to tell And fires lost away / down to hell And as wind trow to take / hero&apos;s hearth To slimy lair / past danger&apos;s berth</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Quest</title><link href="https://mstewartgallus.github.io/poetry/the-ring-and-the-cup/2019/2022/10/18/the-quest.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Quest" /><published>2022-10-18T11:30:00-07:00</published><updated>2022-10-18T11:30:00-07:00</updated><id>https://mstewartgallus.github.io/poetry/the-ring-and-the-cup/2019/2022/10/18/the-quest</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mstewartgallus.github.io/poetry/the-ring-and-the-cup/2019/2022/10/18/the-quest.html">&lt;p&gt;war lost, Two was exiled and turned to banditry
&lt;br /&gt;where he assailed souls from all sides
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;till one day dreaming Two&apos;s heart rose up
&lt;br /&gt;and sleeping in a cave he had a dream
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;lift up, take up, stand up, young son, lost one, lost son
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;go seek the ring - find the cup, rise up young son
&lt;br /&gt;you live today - your heart beats still - and still sings on
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;for none can harm but what you sing, the heart you give
&lt;br /&gt;for bliss or ill this is your life _
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;and you choose how your story ends - not the knife
&lt;br /&gt;for hell or heaven, judgement day or angel&apos;s song 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;no prison gate nor plague nor pain shall bar
&lt;br /&gt;the mercy of the court - stands uncontested
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two find the cup and ring, the treasure that I sing
&lt;br /&gt;and keep on - and on and on, for me, for you
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;all men die, all churches crumble - all this shall fall
&lt;br /&gt;the weight and measure of so much dross - this all 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;just heart and soul - song and word and breath redeem
&lt;br /&gt;the weighty load you carry, wealth or burning coal
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;all sorrow then - just dust of men, thunder
&lt;br /&gt;the beating of the heart and - the singing soul&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><category term="the-ring-and-the-cup" /><category term="2019" /><summary type="html">war lost, Two was exiled and turned to banditry where he assailed souls from all sides</summary></entry></feed>